

ABOUT ME

I am a product designer with experience creating bespoke items and furniture for the hospitality industry and residential

I have over 2 years of experience in the design, development and production of annual collections launched at Salone di Milano and London Design Week. Responsibilities include sample production and development with manufacturers and seasonal travel to check production at the workshops.

Now looking for a new and challenging position to further my professional career.

EXPERIENCE

Product Designer at Bohinc Studio

London (09-2018 - Present)

At Bohinc Studio I have explored furniture and object design, working side by side with the designer and CEO Lara Bohinc. The studio approaches the design of objects from an artistic point of view, where objects are seen as a piece of art. My duties are:

- Assistance with creating designs for new collections. (development of ideas, 3d model and rendering, technical sheets for production).
- Dealing with manufacturers and production of new pieces. This includes visiting the workshops in Portugal and Italy and checking on the production.
- Dealing with worldwide client requests.
- Generate detailed drawings and presentation graphics for client review.
- Organizing orders shipments.
- Assistant at photo shoots.
- Creating content for social media.

Product Designer at Maxim World Ltd

London (05/2017- 07-2018)

Working for a company which specialises in bespoke products for the luxury hospitality sector.

The company provides the design and production service of OS&E products (room & bathroom accessories, food & beverage) made in a variety of materials.

Under the supervision of the team leader my duties were:

- Design and product development according to the briefings (supported by detailed drawings and 3D visual presentations).
- Design new products, introducing new ideas and materials according to the company standard.
- Creation of the month's Newsletter and other graphic design tasks.

OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

Volunteer Worker at Red Cross Spain

Summer 2016

The program is called "Urgent attention to basic needs". It consisted in listening and talking to people in need, trying to make them comfortable and assist with their necessities.

Aquabranding

Intership - Lisboa (07/2015 - 08/2015)

Internship period in the studio, which included Graphic Design and Product Development projects.

- Improvement and development of logotypes for product brands.
- Design and development of packaging and logo for a takeaway container.
- Assisted my supervisor for research purposes.

MOBILE NUMBER: +44 (0) 7592273746 E-MAIL: anacotelovelo@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

SPANISH: Mother language ENGLISH: Full professional

GALICIAN: Mother language PORTUGUESE: Intermediate level

proficiency

EDUCATION

Universidade da Coruña - EUDI University of A Coruña (2012-2016)

Engineering Degree in Industrial Design and Product Development.

IADE Creative University

Lisboa (2014-2015) Erasmus Exchange Programe

The program presented a fantastic opportunity to acquire knowledge, experience, and to learn new skills in another country. The multidisciplinary nature of the school enriched my own methodology and practice.

UAL: Central St. Martins

Short Course in Interior Design

DESIGN SKILLS

Sketching	Creativity	
Modelling	Teamwork	
Rendering	Management	

S

SOFTWARE SKILLS		
Adobe	Modelling	
Photoshop ————	Rhinoceros	
Illustrator	AutoCAD	
InDesign	KeyShot	
After Effects		